<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<EnumCategory xmlns:arrays="http://schemas.microsoft.com/2003/10/Serialization/Arrays" xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="MetraTech">
  <Description>Represents a reason of why a subscription is ended.</Description>
  <EnumMode>EnumValue</EnumMode>
  <Extension i:nil="true" />
  <Name>EndReasonType</Name>
  <Namespace>MetraTech.Metanga</Namespace>
  <Values>
    <EnumValue>
      <Aliases />
      <Description>If end reason of a subscription is set to Expiration, it means that the subscription has expired.</Description>
      <Name>Expiration</Name>
    </EnumValue>
    <EnumValue>
      <Aliases />
      <Description>If end reason of a subscription is set to Renewal, it means that the subscription has been renewed. Renewal implies unsubscribing from the current subscription and creating new one subscription for the same package.Note: This option is not supported by Metanga in current release and will be supported going forward.</Description>
      <Name>Renewal</Name>
    </EnumValue>
    <EnumValue>
      <Aliases />
      <Description>If end reason of a subscription is set to Conversion, it means that the subscription has been converted. Conversion implies unsubscribing from the current subscription and creating new one subscription for a different package.Note: This option is not supported by Metanga in current release and will be supported going forward.</Description>
      <Name>Conversion</Name>
    </EnumValue>
    <EnumValue>
      <Aliases />
      <Description>If end reason of a subscription is set to Unsubscription, it means that the subscription has been unsubscribed.</Description>
      <Name>Unsubscription</Name>
    </EnumValue>
    <EnumValue>
      <Aliases />
      <Description>If end reason of a subscription is set to Termination, it means that the subscription has been terminated. When susbscription is terminated, Metanga generates appropriate termination fee charges. Terminated subscription cannot be edited further.</Description>
      <Name>Termination</Name>
    </EnumValue>
  </Values>
</EnumCategory>