<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<texts id="Localized Errors" type="collection">
  <description>
    The file defines the MAM application errors. The error message are localized.
    When the Metering SDK returns an error to the MAM looks up the message in the MetraTech Global Message Dll.
    (Actually this task is performed by the MDM.)
  </description>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1000">
    <value>[es-MX]E-Mail is not valid</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1001">
    <value>[es-MX]Password does not match confirm password - please try again</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1002">
    <value>[es-MX]Billing Cycle error. The first day of the month must be less than the second day of the month.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1003">
    <value>[es-MX]E-Mail is required</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1004">
    <value>[es-MX]Namespace description not found. Namespace=[NAME_SPACE]</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1005">
    <value>[es-MX]A system error has occurred.  Please have your administrator check the system log, and try again later.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1006">
    <value>[es-MX]An unknown error has occurred.  Please have your administrator check the system log, and try again later.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1007">
    <value>[es-MX]Too many accounts found.  Please narrow your search.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1008">
    <value>[es-MX]Please enter at least one criteria to search on.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1009">
    <value>[es-MX]Please enter a value to search on.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1010">
    <value>[es-MX]This feature is only supported in IE version 4.0 and above.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1011">
    <value>[es-MX]The E-Mail notification failed, Please have your administrator check the system log, and try again later.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1012">
    <value>[es-MX]Subscriber [ACCOUNT_ID] not found by MAM().Subscriber().Find() in SubscriberFound.Asp.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1013">
    <value>[es-MX]Previous account status [PREVIOUS] or new account status [NEW] mismatch error.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1014">
    <value>[es-MX]Method MAM.Find() returned FALSE.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1015">
    <value>[es-MX]Internal error.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1016">
    <value>[es-MX]Internal database error, the credit was not found.  Record count is zero.  Please contact your administrator.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1017">
    <value>[es-MX]Find error - No rowset returned for user [USERNAME].</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1018">
    <value>[es-MX]Impossible to retrieve output session from the AccountCreation metering. Please contact your administrator.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1019">
    <value>[es-MX]Impossible to read the new account id from the output session. Please contact your administrator.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1020">
    <value>[es-MX]Billing Cycle error. The first day of the month must be between 1 and 30 and the second day of the month must be between 2 and 31.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1021">
    <value>[es-MX]Ticketing file [FILENAME] not found.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1022">
    <value>[es-MX]The user name already exists.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_ERROR_DETAIL">
    <value>[es-MX]Details</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1023">
    <value>[es-MX]Cannot get credit card information. Please contact your administrator.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1024">
    <value>[es-MX]Cannot get ACH information. Please contact your administrator.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1025">
    <value>[es-MX]The batch operation failed and all changes were rolled back.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1026">
    <value>[es-MX]You must specify an account for discount distribution by selecting it from the Account Finder.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1027">
    <value>[es-MX]Invalid ancestor account</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1028">
    <value>[es-MX]Invalid payer account</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1029">
    <value>[es-MX]You do not have access to manage:  [ACCOUNT_ID].</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1030">
    <value>[es-MX]Discount account format is invalid.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1031">
    <value>[es-MX]The group has been created.  Please select accounts to add.  Or click cancel to go back.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1032">
    <value>[es-MX]Unable to refresh the account catalog.  Please logout and login again.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1033">
    <value>[es-MX]You must specify at least one account.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1034">
    <value>[es-MX]There are no accounts in your current selection.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1035">
    <value>[es-MX]You must specify a valid account id to describe the hierarchy path.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1036">
    <value>[es-MX]The batch subscription failed for some accounts.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1037">
    <value>[es-MX]Please enter a valid account ID.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1038">
    <value>[es-MX]No transactions found.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1039">
    <value>[es-MX]Select a child transaction</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1040">
    <value>[es-MX]You must compute the adjustment before viewing details or saving it</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1041">
    <value>[TEXT_KEYTERM_PRICEABLE_ITEM] [NAME] [es-MX]has no adjustment types configured.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1042">
    <value>[es-MX]No [TEXT_KEYTERM_PRICEABLE_ITEM] Type with Adjustment(s) found in the Product Catalog.  There are no transactions that can be adjusted.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1043">
    <value>[es-MX]Cannot find the orphan adjustment [SESSIONID].</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1044">
    <value>[es-MX]Please select [ITEM]</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1045">
    <value>[es-MX]Internal Error.  Cannot find the Session ID [SESSIONID] in the transaction rowset</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1046">
    <value>[es-MX]No default payment method was set up for the account.  It has been reset to cash/check.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1047">
    <value>[es-MX]No item selected</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1048">
    <value>[es-MX]MAM_ERROR_1048-Adjustment Display Internal Error</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1049">
    <value>[es-MX]You must enter a valid parent account ID.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1050">
    <value>[es-MX]Please select either a Billing Interval or both the Start Date and End Date for the search.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1051">
    <value>[es-MX]Please select at least one transaction.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1052">
    <value><![CDATA[[es-MX]  The batch template operation failed for some accounts. <br><br> <i>Please note that any account update operations that succeeded will not be rolled back.  However, Group Subscriptions are done in a single transaction.  This means that if there is an error with one of the accounts being placed in a Group Subscription none of them will be added.</i> ]]></value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_1053">
    <value>[es-MX]Account cannot be moved to another namespace.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2000">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while adding the id mapping.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2001">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while removing an id mapping.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2002">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while updating the id mapping.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2003">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while creating the connection.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2004">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while removing the connection.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2005">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while updating the connection dates.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2006">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while moving the connection.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2007">
    <value>[es-MX]An error occurred while creating the [TEXT_KEYTERM_SERVICE_ENDPOINT].  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2008">
    <value>[es-MX]Unable to determine Corporate Account ID from the specified value.  Value should be an account ID or have the format Name (ID).</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2009">
    <value>[es-MX]Unable to determine [TEXT_SE_ID] from the specified value.  Value should be a valid [TEXT_SE_ID] or have the format: Name (ID).</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2010">
    <value>[es-MX]The specified value for [TEXT_SE_ID] does not map to an existing [TEXT_KEYTERM_SERVICE_ENDPOINT].</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2011">
    <value>[es-MX]Failed to delete account template.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2012">
    <value>[es-MX]One or more warnings occurred, Adjustment cannot be saved</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2013">
    <value>[es-MX]Failed to create account template.  Please have your administrator check the system log.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2014">
    <value>[es-MX]No accounts found to apply template to.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="MAM_ERROR_2015">
    <value>[es-MX]The batch operation failed and all changes were rolled back.</value>
  </text>
</texts>