<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<texts id="Main" type="collection">
  <text id="TEXT_Identify_Sessions_Using_SQL">
    <value>Identify Sessions Using SQL</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_An_empty_table_with_the_name_t_rerun_session_">
    <value>An empty table with the name &lt;b&gt;t_rerun_session_</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_has_just_been_created_in_the_database_The">
    <value> has just been created in the database. The</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_in_the_table_name_is_the_current_rerun_id">
    <value> in the table name is the current rerun id.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_You_will_now_need_to_access_the_database_directly">
    <value>You will now need to access the database directly and execute the SQL necessary to populate this table, t_rerun_session_</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_with_the_session_ids_you_wish">
    <value>, with the session ids you wish to backout or resubmit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you have populated the table with the session ids, select &apos;Next Step: Analyze&apos; below to proceed to the &apos;Identify and Analyze&apos; page where you can review what is going to be backed out and resubmitted before any action is taken on these sessions.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_I_will_use_SQL_directly_to_identify_the_records_to_be_backed_out">
    <value>I will use SQL directly to identify the records to be backed out.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Next_Step_Analyze">
    <value>Next Step: Analyze</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Examples">
    <value>Examples</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Essentially_you_are_just">
    <value>Essentially you are just inserting the session ids of the transactions you wish to backout but the ids have to be inserted in a particular way. In addition, the query for inserting failed transaction ids is different from the query for inserting successful transaction ids.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you make a mistake, no problem. As long as you haven't deleted or resubmitted the transactions, even if you have proceed to the next page (the Identify and Analyze page) and discover you have made a mistake, you can update the &lt;b&gt;t_rerun_session_</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_table_by_adding_or">
    <value> table by adding or deleting records with out starting over as long as you select &apos;Reanalyze&apos; at the top of the next page to update the summary information before continuing on to actually delete or resubmit the transactions.</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Usage_Transaction_Example">
    <value>Usage Transaction Example</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_For_Example">
    <value>For example, if the following query selecting usage for account 137 that was processed before February 2005 represented the sessions you wanted to backout</value>
  </text>  
  <text id="TEXT_Then_you_would_execute">
    <value>Then you would execute the following query to insert these same records into the rerun table</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Failed_Transaction_Example">
    <value>Failed Transaction Example</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Failed_Transaction_Example_Content">
    <value>For example, if the following query selecting failed transactions that are new, happened in a service whose name ends with &apos;testservice&apos; and were metered before February 2005 represented the sessions you wanted to backout</value>
  </text>
  <text id="TEXT_Then_you_would_execute_the_following_query">
    <value>Then you would execute the following query to insert these same records into the rerun table</value>
  </text>
</texts>